automotiveaddicts.com 2009-06-23

# Privacy Policy | Automotive Addicts

Browse >

[Home](http://www.automotiveaddicts.com/ "Browse to: Home") / Privacy Policy 

### Privacy Policy/Terms of Service

At Automotive Addicts we respect your right to privacy and we understand that, as a visitor to automotiveaddicts.com, you prefer to control your own personal information and preferences. For this reason, we may ask you to register or to provide personal information and preferences when you visit our upcoming forum area.

We will guard the personal information you share with us to ensure the content, services, and advertising that we provide on automotiveaddicts.com are always tailored to your current, designated preferences.

Beyond our representatives and affiliates, Automotive Addicts does not offer or allow the selling of any user-provided information to third parties.

If you choose not to register, you can still visit and view the Automotive Addicts Forum; however, you will not have access to post on our forum. Personal information that you post to online forums is accessible by other forum participants whether it be guests or registered users.

### Displayed Image Usage Policy

Automotive Addicts owns and retains the copyrights in all displayed images except as noted. No copyright license (either express or implied) is granted to the user. Images are available for resale and cannot be used for any commercial purposes without permission.

It is generally illegal to copy, reproduce or distribute copyrighted information or materials (including photographs) without the consent of the owner of such copyright. Generally, the photographer is the owner of the copyright of a photograph or image. Unless otherwise clearly indicated, you should assume that anything and everything you see or read on this site is copyrighted and may not be used or copied by you except as explicitly provided in this site, or by applicable law or otherwise without the express prior written consent of Automotive Addicts or the copyright owner. This prohibition means you may not transmit, mirror, modify or re-distribute any images or text from this site without the express prior written permission of Automotive Addicts or the copyright owner. You may download and print images and text from this site only for your private, non-commercial use. Any other use requires the prior consent of Automotive Addicts or the copyright owner. YOU ALSO REPRESENT THAT YOU ARE THE OWNER OR ARE AUTHORIZED BY THE COPYRIGHT OWNER TO USE ANY COPYRIGHTED MATERIALS SUBMITTED OR PROVIDED BY YOU. UNAUTHORIZED USE MAY BE IN VIOLATION OF THE LAW AND COULD RESULT IN LIABILITY BY YOU.

Any images contained in or displayed by Automotive Addicts on this site, other than as submitted by you, are the property of Automotive Addicts or are used by Automotive Addicts Staff with the consent of the copyright holder and persons if any, appearing in such images. Subject to paragraph 2 hereof, the use by you of any such images (or any portions thereof) without the express written consent of Automotive Addicts or the copyright holder is prohibited. UNAUTHORIZED USE MAY BE IN VIOLATION OF THE LAW AND COULD RESULT IN LIABILITY BY YOU.

### The use of log files (cookies)

Automotive Addicts may offer free forum membership to all visitors in the event that we have an open forum. In order to establish membership, visitors are requested to provide both very limited personal information and preferences. This information is stored and protected by your user-established User-Name and Password.

There is an additional ” Log me on automatically each visit ” option. By selecting it, you allow Automotive Addicts to store your User-Name and password so you can access the forum without re-signing in. The sign-in information is stored until you explicitly sign out. Automotive Addicts remembers you by placing a log file (cookie) that contains only enough information to identify you upon return visits. A “cookie” is a small line of text that is stored with your web browser for record-keeping purposes and helps Automotive Addicts (forum) provide better service to you. Your browser has options to accept, reject, or provide you with notice when a cookie is sent.

No information, other than that found in the Membership cookie, will be accessed by any system on our site. Access to your forum membership information always requires both your User-Name and Password.

Automotive Addicts also utilizes visitor log files (cookies) and hosted tracking with our website. Once a user enters our site, a cookie follows them through their click stream path. Examples of information being collected by these cookies and the hosted tracking include the number of times a user came to our site(s), and the paths they took to get there. Our site uses the data collected from website visitor cookies and hosted tracking in aggregate form only and does not collect any personally identifiable information.

E-mail  

Automotive Addicts would like to receive your comments and questions about this Privacy Policy: Please address comments or questions regarding the Automotive Addicts Privacy Policy to one of the email addresses listed. Automotive Addicts may occasionally update, amend, or change this Privacy Policy based on user feedback and as needed or appropriate. If we decide to materially change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and will e-mail the information to our users so that wish to receive such an update.

### Advertisements

AutomotiveAddicts.com will do it’s best to monitor the content and activity of all site-wide advertisements. We do not guarantee the validity or directly control any links or content found on our advertisers or sponsors web pages. If you do not agree with practices of a particular advertiser or sponsor, please contact the appropriate owner or authority of the specific site in question. Automotive Addicts encourages you to read the privacy statements of our advertiser or sponsor pages; their privacy practices may differ from ours. If you would like to inquire about sponsorship or advertising on AutomotiveAddicts.com please [visit our Advertisement section here](http://www.automotiveaddicts.com/advertise-on-automotiveaddicts). 

### Links

Our website may contain links to other sites. Automotive Addicts assumes no responsibility for the content or the privacy policies and practices of such websites. Automotive Addicts encourages you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites; their privacy practices may differ from ours.
